Boss , I need a bathroom break !
Please .
Dear Lord , help me !
Get the hell out of here .
Well , that 's what you get for drinking on the job , Sloane .
Hey , Sloane , take it easy !
Sloane ! Sloane ! Damn it ! Sloane !
You can do it !
Sloane . Sloane .
Uhh ...
Dear God help us .
# Hush , little baby , don 't say a word #
# Mama 's gonna buy you ... #
He 's so beautiful .
That 's the ugliest thing I ever saw .
Don 't worry about it , Tommy .
You don 't have to look pretty to work down at the slaughterhouse .
What is that diseased freak still doing out here ?
We closed for good now .
Uh , I think he likes it here , sir .
Ain 't no reason for that ugly beast to still be here .
Jess , we need to get that oversized retard the hell out of here .
We , sir ?
Just you .
Hello , Hewitt .
We 're shutting down the place today .
You know that ' cause I done told you .
Shutting down for good .
We ain 't packing no more meat .
Ain 't killing no more animals so ...
you just leave the equipment . You just get on home now , okay ?
You gotta go , I said !
You gotta get the hell out of here , you dumb animal !
What are you doing ?
Shh ! Keep your voice down .
This is how you sneak up on ' em ,
- how you catch ' em . - Catch who ?
Gooks in the swamp .
Eric , the only thing you 're gonna catch in this water is disease .
- Chrissie , come on . - No , I 'm not going in that water .
Consider it the last wish of a soldier .
Oh , no .
No , you 've been getting last wishes this whole past week , G.I. Joe .
And you call yourself a patriot .
- You know what I think is patriotic ? - What ?
Me driving you across state to go to Vietnam . Again .
You goin ' all the way to Vietnam , baby ?
No , honey , base camp 's far enough for me , trust me .
Just try to relax , baby ,
' cause today I 'm going to use my tongue
in ways the Lord never intended .
- How 's that sound ? - Okay .
# All right now #
# Baby , it 's all right now #
# Whoa ... #
Mmm ...
# Let me tell you now #
# I took her home to my place #
# Watching every move on her face ... #
This may come as a shock to you , but most men
are into this kind of thing .
I 'm sorry .
I 'm just a little distracted , Bail .
I mean , I just keep thinking ,
how does a person go back there ?
You know , how do you do that ?
It doesn 't make him any more heroic than you , baby , okay ?
Yeah , but he thinks I 'm going with him , Bail .
Eric thinks I 'm going to Vietnam with him .
Well , he 's your brother , he loves you .
You know , he 'll get over it , okay ?
Just close your eyes .
Let me see your hand .
You 're gonna love this .
Can I look ?
Yeah .
Eric , you got that from a Cracker Jack box !
Wha ... I ... I had to eat 17 batches to find the one I wanted .
How many ?
- Two . - Okay , girls or boys ?
One of each .
And what are their names ?
- Bonnie and Clyde . - No .
- Come on . - Bobby and Janis .
And where are us and the kids gonna live ?
California . Right by the water .
Don 't leave me .
I ain 't never gonna leave you , beautiful .
I 'll give you everything you want , baby .
Starting with this .
This is what you 're gonna tell him ...
you 're going to walk right up to Eric ,
and you 're gonna tell him that you 're going to Mexico
and you 're not gonna join him in this stupid war ,
no matter what some draft card says .
Okay ?
Get your bony ass ready , soldier ! Moving out at 1700 hours .
What 's 1700 hours ?
You better be getting some , Dean .
What the hell are you still doing here ?
Go home . We 're out of business .
You and your family are the only ones stupid enough
to still be living in this town .
Your kind belong in this shithole .
Operator .
May I help you ?
You 're gonna have to speak more clearly , ma 'am .
I don 't understand . You 're gonna have to speak more clearly .
I 'm your friend , Hewitt .
Come on , y 'all . Look alive now .
Take one last look at that motel over there
' cause this here 's your lodging for the next two days .
What , are you gonna put mints on our pillows too ?
I 'll tuck you in special every night .
We 're going on a road trip !
# Hey well , I 'm the friendly stranger in the black sedan #
# Won 't you hop inside my car ? #
# Got peaches , got candy , I 'm a loveable man #
# Take you to the nearest star #
- # And I 'll love you # - # Love you #
- # I 'll need you # - # Need you #
# I want you , got to have you , child #
# Great God in heaven you know I love you ... #
So what are you gonna miss the most ?
- Hmm ? - When you 're gone ,
what are you gonna miss the most ?
Fishing for compliments here ?
No , never .
- She is fishing . - I am not .
Come on , tell me .
Besides you ?
Nothing .
I mean , family and all , sure ,
but Dean 's gonna be right there with me .
- Right , Deano ? - Hoo-ha .
Oh , cool !
Don 't you just love a man on a motorcycle ?
It 's like Peter Fonda in " Easy Rider . "
- Hey guys , don 't stare . - Coming up fast .
Y 'all , don 't stare at them .
Baby , they 're coming a little too close .
Whoa whoa whoa .
Stop it !
Hey ! Fuck you !
Hey , we better get out of here . Get down .
Hey ! Get off , asshole .
Drive faster !
Man , what the hell 's your problem ?
- You okay , baby ? - Yeah .
- You 're all right ? - Yeah , I 'm good .
- Thomas in there ? - No , he ain 't here .
We got a ... we got a situation on our hands here .
I just came back from the slaughterhouse .
That ' tarded nephew of yours killed a man .
Now I 'm gonna have to apprehend him .
I thought you might want to accompany me ,
help finesse the situation , as it were .
You know what else Jesse was saying ?
Honestly , he tells me that you can bring a horse
to " organism " using your finger .
You believe that shit ? No , it 's what he said .
Who 's the fool that tested that theory out , I 'd like to know ?
God damn , I wouldn 't mind doing it .
But I 'm just saying , a bunch of sore horses
running around out in some farm ...
Anyway , staying around this town ,
there 's no more jobs , no more money ,
no more food . It 's downright suicidal .
And I 'm the last bit of law enforcement that 's left .
Hell , I 'm moving to Michigan next week .
I often ask myself , " What makes a man a killer ? "
I don 't mind saying : You raised that retard right ,
me and you , we ain 't taking this drive right now .
You can 't have a creature like that around normal folk ,
- that 's what I 'm saying . - He ain 't retarded . He 's misunderstood .
Oh , shit , there he is ! Jesus Christ .
You stay put .
I 'll let you know when I need you .
Put down the weapon , boy !
I seen what you did back there , Hewitt .
This doesn 't have to be difficult unless 'n you make it so .
Just put the weapon down .
Don 't be stupid .
I think we 've got a problem , Sheriff .
Shit , I just killed the whole fucking sheriff 's department .
Damn , I wondered what that felt like .
You really think you 're something in that outfit , don 't you ?
Here 's your pants . Supper 's on the table .
Ladies love a man in uniform .
That slaughterhouse meant more to this town than them fools will ever know .
Just a matter of time now
before this town 's overrun by bikers and hippies .
Most families have already fled .
Well , I say let ' em go .
Let them flee to the hills and the cities
that pollute our air , and our water and our minds .
Us , we 're staying right here .
The ashes of six generations of Hewitts
have been tilled into the soil of this farm .
We will never abandon the place of our birth .
We 're on our own now , people .
And alone
we will rise above it all .
People may not remember what we say here tonight ,
but they sure as shit gonna remember what we do .
Thanks to the good sheriff here ,
we ain 't gonna go hungry tonight .
Matter of fact ,
we ain 't never gonna starve again .
Mm-mm-mm .
Charlie , say grace .
Mama , I told you Charlie 's dead .
It 's Hoyt now , Sheriff Hoyt .
Lord , thank You for all this bounty that You 've
provided for us here this evening . Amen .
Tommy , you come on in here and join us for supper .
Come on now , son .
Oh baby , look ! Come on , can we stop at that store ?
It 's just like the one in California . Please ?
Yeah yeah .
Come on , Bail , you 'll love this .
These places have tons of character .
Y 'all have some beautiful things in here , ma 'am .
Okay ...
It 'll take you a little while to get used to things in ' Nam .
The people ,
the smells , but ...
But what ?
You 'd be amazed at the things you can get used to .
Um , is everything okay with you and Dean ?
Uh , what do you mean ?
Bailey , come on . You guys have been exchanging odd glances this whole trip .
Oh ...
Excuse me , ma 'am , can you tell me where the bathroom is , please ?
Through the back .
Pretty .
But pretty only goes skin-deep . Ugly is to the bone .
Leave them be .
Come on , Bailey .
Look , we 've been through a lot together .
Whatever it is , you can tell me .
Me and Dean are going to Mexico .
He 's not gonna go with Eric .
And uh , he 's not going to Vietnam .
Chrissie ...
- what do you have to say ? - I say , go .
Get the hell away from this war , okay ? Just cling to what you got .
Then why are you letting Eric go back ?
- It 's just in him . - What 's in him ?
- The war . - What do you mean ?
Look , you do something long enough , eventually you start to like it .
Hah !
- Bitch . - Scared the titties right off her .
God damn it .
Broke my mirror .
You think the girls are gonna be all right
driving back alone after they drop us off ?
Oh , I 'm not worried about them , Dean .
Are you sure you got nothing to tell me ?
Can we go ?
You all right ?
Yeah ... let 's just go .
You didn 't even buy anything , baby .
Yeah , it was ... it was nothing like the one in California .
I guess we 'll just have to go back to that one then .
What are you doing , man ?
- What the hell are you doing ? - I 'm not going , Eric .
What do you mean , you 're not going ?
I 'm not going , Eric !
You think I don 't hear you at night , man ,
in your sleep , wailing from what you 've done over there ?
Now , how could you want that for me ?
I 'm glad Dad 's not here to see this .
What , his son the coward ?
Well , guess what , Eric , I am not like you !
All right ?
I am not ready for this shit ! I have no problem
with the Vietcong over in Vietnam or whatever ...
What the hell do you think I 'm going back for , huh ?
- I 'm going back for you ! - Stop it !
You think you 're the only one who 's ever been scared ?
You think I wasn 't scared ? You think I 'm still not scared ?
Shut up !
What does she want ?
Pull over ! Pull over !
Oh God . Jesus Christ , don 't pull over !
Shit , she 's got a gun , Eric .
Eric !
Shut up ! Stay calm .
- What are we gonna do ? - Eric , she 's pulling ...
Oh my God !
Look out !
God ...
Chrissie .
Buddy , Dean , Deano ...
I 'm gonna get you help . I 'm gonna find Chrissie .
Chrissie !
Wow , man , I am impressed .
- Y 'all are tougher than I thought . - What do you want from us ?
Oh ... everything .
How about we get this robbery thing out of the way , huh ?
Fuck .
You play along , and I won 't have to kill this fucking cop or you . Get up !
I 'm glad you 're here , officer .
Oh , I just bet you are .
Whoa !
Sir .
You sit down and you stay right there .
You kids okay ?
Why don 't you step out of the car , if you don 't mind ?
- He shot her ! He shot her ! - She can 't move , sir . She needs help .
Sir , I can 't find my girlfriend .
Get a grip on yourself , son .
Sir , I can 't find ...
Now , that was for your own good .
Okay , come on kids . Let 's get out of the car now .
Sir , she 's ... she 's really badly hurt .
Right , well okay , kids .
I 'm gonna ask you nicely one more time .
Get out of the fuckin ' car or I 'm gonna blow your fuckin ' head off .
Come on , you can make it . Ooh-ee !
You kids must have been hauling ass .
Look at the fucking mess you made .
Hey hey hey . Come on now .
I 'm just here to help you .
Come on now .
- Go on . I ain 't gonna hurt you . - Sir , sir , please .
I 'm not gonna hurt you .
You fucking motherfucker !
See there ? That didn 't even hurt , did it ?
There ain 't no fire in this accident .
Which one of you assholes burned his draft card ?
Get on over here , boys .
- Come on , get over here . - No .
God damn it , get over here !
Which one of you boys ' name is Dean Hill ?
Honey , you 're name ain 't Dean , is it ?
I am , sir ...
I 'm Dean .
Well , hey , dean . Good to meet you .
You kids took one
big , nasty , giant shit
right in my backyard .
Now we do know that you 're a coward , right , Dean ?
I 'm gonna to give you a chance to die a hero .
All right , get her in there , God damn it .
I 'm starting to think you like wasting my time , blondie .
Hurry up !
- I saw Chrissie . - You did ?
She 's okay . Just don 't say anything .
- Where is she ? - Shut up .
Hey , Monty , come pick up this damn wreck .
It 's about a quarter mile south of Hodd 's place .
There 's a motorcycle too .
Is having a dead biker chick ride shotgun proper police procedure , sir ?
Honey , if that was your mama ,
would you want me to stick her in the trunk like a dead animal ?
I just think this is bullshit .
You got something to say about this bullshit , do you , Dean ?
No , sir .
You wouldn 't lie to me , would you , Dean ?
Where is the gun ?
You look through all this shit on the road ?
Is that how we agreed you 'd address me over official FCC airwaves ?
No , " Sheriff . "
Oh ...
pretty little rascal , ain 't you ?
Don 't you have to read us our rights or something , Sheriff ?
Who in the hell put you assholes in charge anyway ?
You see , that badge is the authority around here .
And I ask the questions .
And what brings you kids here ?
Sir , we were just passing through ,
on my way to reenlist , sir .
A doughboy . Hot damn .
I was in the army myself almost a year .
Marines , sir .
Six of one , half dozen of the other .
Heh , don 't make no damn difference .
You look kind of young to me .
Where was you stationed ?
Vietnam , sir .
Vietnam . Really ?
You kill any commies ?
Uh , a handful of gooks , sir .
Where are you taking us ?
Where are you taking us , sir ?
How was it over there ?
Well , it 's a ... it 's a different culture .
But you 'd be amazed at the things you get used to over there , sir .
You don 't say .
This the sheriff station ?
No , it 's Mama 's house .
Oh ! Don 't even think about it here .
What are we gonna do ?
I 'm gonna kill this motherfucker .
Hey !
You kids best not be making a mess in my car or you 'll clean it up .
- He knows , Eric . - What ?
He knows you 're not me .
- No , he doesn 't , Dean . - Hey , Tommy !
- Stay the course . - We 're out here !
Come on , boy , get over here !
- What is that ? - Get the lead out of your ass !
Come on , big guy !
What is that ?
Go ahead , get her on out of there .
Come on , private !
Oh my God .
I 'm gonna get us out of here , okay ?
Dean ! Stay with me !
I need you to be a soldier .
People are gonna come looking for ' em , I know it .
You have made a big mistake !
Boy , are you dumb .
Nobody 's gonna miss those creatures , not one person .
Not now , not when they gone .
Let 's see . Anything in here ?
A bunch of shit .
Oh ...
You little bastard , I know you 've got more in there .
Come on , Tommy , ain 't no different than the slaughterhouse .
Meat 's meat , bones bones .
Get it done .
My daddy always told me
that if you want to be a good farmer you gotta keep your livestock clean .
Clean goat is a happy goat .
What the hell do you want from us , man ?
Are you happy yet ?
Hey !
H ... hey , help us . Help us down , please .
I don 't get involved in his affairs . No .
Please , help me .
Please , please .
No ! No !
Help me ! No !
No !
- No ! - Bailey .
- I didn 't know . - Didn 't know what ?
I didn 't know you were going back there for me .
Let 's figure out how to get out of here , Dean .
By God , I 'm gonna make a soldier out of you yet !
No ! Please , please !
Are you ashamed of your country , Dean ?
No , please ! No !
What do you think , soldier ?
What would be the proper punishment for treason ?
Just please let him go , sir . No !
I can 't make out a word you 're saying , you know it , asshole ?
You 're killing him , sir ! Please !
No no no ! Please , sir !
Ain 't nothing I hate worse than a draft-dodging hippie protester .
I 'm Dean !
It was my draft card !
It was my draft card ! It was my draft card !
And you 'd just stand here and let him die .
Sir , could you let him breathe , please ?
Please , can you let him breathe ?
- My apologies . - Eric !
Oh shit !
Well , so now you want to play soldier . Is that it ?
Your brother saved your life .
I 'm gonna fucking cut your head off .
Yeah , you just keep sweet-talking me , dumpling .
Help me !
Back in 1952 , Korean War ,
yours truly was a P.O.W.
That 's " prisoner of war " for you ,
and I know what in the hell I 'm talking about .
Used to be Sergeant Major Hoyt .
Back in those days there wasn 't no rules .
No regulations like there are today .
You got captured , you had two choices :
You starve to death or survive .
Now , you had to eat . Rations were scarce .
So , well , about once a week
some poor soul was chosen .
Chosen ?
You fucking idiot ! I just told you we had to eat !
Ain 't you listening to me ? Huh ?
I 'd say that 's the ultimate sacrifice for your country , wouldn 't you ?
Why are you doing this ?
Got to get you cleaned up .
We 're gonna have company .
You don 't want to look dirty for company , do you ?
Huh ?
This is your lucky day !
Now what happens if you kids drive all the way up to Austin
just to find out that you don 't even qualify to be in the army ?
I 'm concerned about your physical fitness here !
Now , doesn 't that make you feel special ?
Huh ? Don 't it ?
Please .
That would be , " Please , Sheriff . "
- You got it ? - Please , Sheriff .
Hey , boy , there you go . I knew you could do that .
That wasn 't so hard , was it ?
How would you like to just stand right up here today
and just walk right on out of here , huh ?
I 'd like that , Sheriff .
Yeah , well , freedom ain 't free . You know that , right ?
What you gonna do is 20 push-ups .
20 push-ups stand between you and freedom .
This shit is what heroes are made of , you know ?
Well , come on , I 'm waiting !
Let 's get with the program , sunshine !
Come on , you can do it ! Get those push-ups now !
No !
Shh , now don 't cry .
Don 't cry .
No .
No !
You shut your cocksucker , you son of a bitch !
One !
Whoa , that was a really fine push-up there . One ...
Two ...
We 've got ourselves a regular American hero here , ain 't we ?
Three .
Come on , sweetheart .
# Hush , little baby #
# Don 't say a word ... #
Ow !
# Mama 's gonna buy you a mockingbird ... #
Eight .
What 's it gonna be ?
You 're gonna be the motherfucker who eats ?
Or are you gonna be the poor sorry motherfucker
who gets ate ?
# If that mockingbird don 't sing ... #
# Mama 's gonna buy you a golden ring ... #
Don 't give up , Dean ! Show this motherfucker !
Show me that you ain 't as fucked up
as the rest of your useless goddamn generation .
Eighteen !
# If that golden ... #
- Come on ! - Nine ...
# ... Is gonna buy you a looking glass ... #
Go !
That 's only half of one . That don 't count , boy !
Don 't give up , Dean !
- 20 . - Yeah !
Don 't cry .
No !
- No . - I never had me a little girl .
Got more guts than I thought you had , boy .
I 'm a man of my word . You 're free to go .
I 'm gonna fucking kill you !
My money says he ain 't going nowhere .
Stop !
Please , stop !
Please stop !
Look ... my friends , they ...
they have my friends , okay ? They 're in a house over there through the woods . I ...
Look , they have your friend . They took your friend .
I saw you both at the store .
He shot her . The sheriff shot her .
Show me where .
Weather has been so hot lately .
It 's important to drink your liquids , you know ?
The body needs to hydrate .
I got me some of that breakfast tea ... that 's what they call it ...
and I fixed me up a batch of that
and I had it over a big fruit jar of ice with plenty of sugar .
And I had that breakfast tea for dinner .
Tastes like paradise .
Not a bit of difference .
Iced tea .
Yeah , iced tea .
You know what else is good ?
- Iced coffee . - Oh .
Delicious . With them little cinnamon sprinkles .
Dean . Dean !
Dean , you did good . But we gotta hide , okay ?
Come on ! Come on !
Do you have any idea where the hell we 're going ?
Yes , it 's ...
it 's here somewhere .
Sometimes ...
I just can 't stop eating them little chocolates .
They 're so good .
I put coconut in them .
Oh , sweet Jesus .
Hoyt ! Hoyt !
Come here ! Hoyt !
Eric !
- He 's in here ! - Eric ! Get me out of here !
- Shut your mouth ! - Oh , my !
He 's here ! He 's here ! He 's here !
Help ! Help !
There 's keys over there on the counter .
Damn you ! A man 's home is his fucking castle !
- What the fuck are you doing in here ? - Oh no !
Hey !
Find the truck . Go ! I 'll get Dean ! I 'll get Dean !
Unlock the door !
Thomas , Thomas , get up here ! I need you !
Come on , Dean , come on .
Hey ! Get back here , you skinny bitch !
No !
Come on , we 're gonna get out of here .
Dean , go ! Go ! Come on !
Shoot me , you asshole !
You 're not a soldier ! You hold that gun like a fucking girl !
Get out of my way .
You 're not a candy-ass , are you , Sheriff ?
Pull the fucking trigger !
I ain 't finished with you yet .
Well ... let 's just go see if we caught anything .
Well well well ...
it 's a good thing you didn 't go to Vietnam .
Something like this might 've happened .
You don 't like playing with me anymore because I 'm a pussy .
That 's what you said .
Well , my nephew Tommy ain 't no pussy .
Maybe you want to play with him for a little while .
That 's it .
Okay , so what are we gonna do ?
We ? I 'm gonna get my girlfriend .
No no , look . What about my friends ?
- What ? - My friends .
Fuck your friends .
You 're on your own .
You asshole !
Shit .
Dean , Dean . Oh fuck . Thank God .
What happened ?
- Chrissie . Oh , thank God . - Oh , Jesus Christ .
- No no no . Don 't ! - I 'm sorry .
Just stay still . Okay , are you okay ? You 're okay .
They 're psycho .
Come on , where 's Eric and Bailey ? Come on .
In the house .
You need to go get help , Chrissie .
Okay ?
There 's no help to go for .
I have to go in there . You 're gonna stay here . I 'm gonna come get you , okay ?
Okay .
Don 't you think you 're gonna go anyplace , huh ?
I love you .
No ! Come on ! You don 't ... you don 't have to do this , man , please .
No ! No . No !
No !
You don 't have to do this .
You son of a bitch !
Fuck you !
Fucker .
Huh ?
What the fuck ...
Oh shit !
- Uh , he shot me ! Uh ! - Shut up ! Shut up !
Where 's the girl ?
I 'm gonna blow your head off . Tell me where the girl is .
I 'm shot ! Shit !
How many times I gotta tell you not to play with guns ?
Oh , Jesus , oh ...
Now look what you 've done to yourself .
- I didn 't do it . - Stop your damn whining , Uncle Monty .
Mama , get some towels in here .
Uncle Monty made a mess .
Sheriff .
Who in the hell are you ?
- What do you want , boy ? - I want my girl .
Take me to her or I 'm gonna blow your head off .
Okay , all right .
- Where is she ? - Thomas !
Hey ! Do not fuck around . Where is the girl ?
Come on .
Help me !
Thomas !
Thomas , where 're you at ?
Eric , are you okay ?
What are you doing here ? You gotta get out of here .
- You 're ... you 're gonna be okay . - How bad is it ? Tell me .
- No ! No ! - It 's all right . I can 't feel it .
- I 'm gonna get you ... it 's okay . - Did he cut it off ?
- It 's okay . - I can 't feel it .
No ! No !
I 'm cold .
How ... how many ?
- Three . - Boys or girls ?
All boys .
What are their names ?
Paul and Christopher ...
and Eric .
Okay . Okay . It 's gonna be okay .
I promise . I promise , okay ?
Take it easy . There she is .
Help me .
That 's not her .
Shit , that ain 't her .
You don 't want to see the other girl .
Just shoot him !
You dumb son of a bitch .
Get him , Tommy , come on !
Damn it ! Come on , Tommy .
This is one of those assholes
who used to fuck with you in the schoolyard , Tommy .
Come on , Tommy , get over here ! Get that thing going !
Let 's go , Tommy ! Come on !
Crank it up ! Let 's go !
What it is , asshole !
Yeah !
You beautiful bastard , you !
You fucking asshole !
You son of a bitch ! Comin ' in my fucking house ...
Oh , God .
You have to get out of here .
- No no no ! - Get out of here .
- No ! - Yes , Chrissie , please .
Hide !
What are you doing ?
Don 't . No . What are you ...
No !
Thomas ! Tommy .
Thomas , quit playing with your fucking dolls and get up here !
I 'm glad you brought your little buddy .
Hmm , I like your new face .
Come on , Tommy , get up here .
Please ! Please !
Help !
Please , please , somebody help !
Now this will take your fever down , all right ?
See what you 've done ?
You killed that sheriff and you started up a whole whirlwind .
Mama , please stop your damn bellyaching .
Uncle Monty , I love you .
You know that , and I always do what 's right by you , don 't I ?
And you trust me , don 't you ?
Yeah , I trust you . Just do something .
Take care of you .
Get in here , boy !
- Uh ! Ow ! - Oh , I 'm sorry .
Tommy !
- Now , this ain 't gonna hurt ... - Huh ?
... much .
What 's that on your face ?
Mama , you get over there and hold Uncle Monty .
- Why ? - ' Cause he ain 't gonna like this much ,
that 's why .
- No ! - What the fuck is this ?
Surgery . Come on , Tommy .
- No ! - Oh my God !
Oh , bullshit . Look at that !
Now , Tommy , that 's goddamn sloppy .
That 'll get infected . Even him up . Come on .
- Huh ? - What ?
- Sheriff , no , stop ! - No !
There you go . Nice work , Tommy .
What did you do that for ?
Balance .
I 'll get Tommy to wrap this up .
Please , somebody help .
Okay . Shh .
You 're gonna be okay , okay ?
Shh shh , I 'm sorry .
It 's okay . You 're safe .
They know you 're here .
I 'll have Mama throw on another plate for supper .
You ... you can stay ?
I think we need a little more garlic in this one .
Mama , a little more garlic in this one .
I 'll go set the table .
Oh , shit !
It 's okay , Mama . Just wash it off . It 'll be fine .
Don 't step on the fingers .
What the hell are they doing on the floor , anyway ?
Good thing you keep a clean house .
I wonder whose tongue this is .
That 's that fuckin ' biker .
# Hush little baby , don 't say a word #
# Mama 's gonna buy you #
# A mockingbird #
# If that mockingbird don 't sing #
# Mama 's gonna buy you #
# A golden ring ... #
# If that golden ring turns brass #
# Mama 's gonna buy you a looking glass ... #
Why are you doing this ?
No talking until after I 've said grace , asshole .
Now ...
let 's give thanks for the bounty that 's been given us .
Bow your heads .
I was hungry and He gave me meat .
I was thirsty and He gave me drink .
I was a stranger and He took me in .
This family has endured through adversity and pain .
- We have endured . - Dean .
We have prevailed .
We will never ever go hungry again .
Amen .
I have a question for you .
One that involves the family tree , the ...
lineage , if you will ,
So I guess this one 's for the table .
You guys fuck all your cousins
or just the ones you find attractive ?
You blasphemous bitch !
This is redemption , lady ! That 's what this is !
Oh , you 're all gonna pay for your sins . That 's right !
And especially you !
Mama ... go take care of Uncle Monty .
You know what , Mama ?
I don 't think this one likes your cooking .
But who gives a shit ?
She 's gonna be sucking her soup through a straw
for some time to come now , ain 't she ?
Come on , Monty , take a sip .
You gotta have something to build up your strength .
Please do it .
Just do whatever you 're gonna do , you bunch of degenerates !
I will not have you speak ill of this family .
Come on , now , open your mouth .
No . No . No .
Set her free , child .
No ! No !
No ! No ! No ! No !
Take that one downstairs !
No , you stay away from me , you fucking animal !
You get the fuck away from me ! No !
Get your hands off me !
You dirty animal !
No ! Dean ! Dean !
Can 't you see ? Your friend ain 't with us no more .
No ! No ! No !
Here we go .
Dean ! Help ! No !
No !
Hey !
Where in the hell you going , bitch ?
She 's gonna tell them all what we done .
There comes a time when every boy becomes a man .
You motherfucker !
Now we 'll see what kind of soldier you are , Sheriff .
One !
That was beautiful form , Sheriff !
Two ! Halfway doesn 't count , dickhead !
Three ! Is that all you got ? Is that all you fucking got ?
Fucker ! You killed my girlfriend !
You fucking asshole !
Fuck you !
My money says you 're not going anywhere .
Fuck .
Chrissie !
From 1969 to 1973
the Hewitt family murdered 33 people across the state of Texas .
To this day their killing spree is universally considered
one of the most notorious and perversely sadistic crimes
in the annals of American history :
The Texas Chainsaw Massacre .